Marvin Carmack papers, 1920-2007 C503
Indiana University Archives
- Research, 1920-2007 (Box 4)
  - Willgerodt Reaction Lectures (Box 12)
    - 1944 (Box 12)
    - 1944-1948 (Box 12)
    - Undated (Box 12)
  - Willgerodt Reaction Notes and Slides, 1963 (Box 12)
  - Willgerodt Reaction Papers, 1945-1946 (Box 13)
  - Willgerodt Reaction Pattison Thesis, 1947 (Box 13)
  - Wilds, A.L., 1947-1948 (Box 13)
  - William A. Pryor Materials, 1960 (Box 13)
  - Winthrop Chemical Company, 1947 (Box 13)
  - Woodrow, Carroll, 1948-1951 (Box 13)
  - Xeroxes of Drawings, undated (Box 13)
  - Zoccon Corporation Materials, 1973 (Box 13)
  - Zurich Research Notes, 1949-1950 (Box 13)
- Teaching, 1936-1978 (Box 14)
  - Lecture Notes, 1936-1978 (Box 14)
    - 1,2,5-Thiadiazole Chemistry Notes, 1955 (Box 14)
    - Alkaloid Course Materials, 1952 (Box 14)
    - Alkaloid Material, undated (Box 14)
    - Amines Materials, undated (Box 14)
    - Animal Scents Lecture Slides, undated (Box 14)
    - C-65, 1942 (Box 14)
    - C-109 Notes, 1950-1951 (Box 14)
      Conditions Governing Access
      (RESTRICTED MATERIALS REMOVED)
    - C-109 Lectures Fall and Spring, 1947-1948 (Box 14)
    - C-114-761 Qualitative Organic Course Materials, 1948 (Box 14)
    - C-341 Course Materials, 1966 (Box 14)
    - C-342 Course Materials (Box 14)
      - 1967-1968 (Box 14)
      - 1968 (Box 14)
    - C-540 Seminar Course Notes, 1961-1962 (Box 14)
    - C-543 Organic Reactions I (Box 14)
      - 1961-1962 (Box 14)
      - 1965-1966 (Box 14)
    - C-543 Organic Reactions II, 1964-1965 (Box 14)
    - C-543 Wenkert-Sigel Notes, 1963-1964 (Box 14)
    - C-643 Active Notes (Box 14)
      - 1961-1965 (Box 14)
      - 1963-1965 (Box 14)
    - C-643 Communication with Chemicals Lecture Notes, 1965-1966 (Box 15)
    - C-643 Natural Products, 1969-1970 (Box 15)
    - C-643 Natural Products Course Materials, 1965-1966 (Box 15)
    - C-643 Natural Products Chemistry, 1965-1966 (Box 15)
    - C-643 Organic Natural Products Materials, 1969 (Box 15)
    - C-643 Projection Slides, undated (Box 15)
    - C-648 Natural Products Seminar, 1958-1959 (Box 15)
    - C-648 Materials (Box 15)
      - 1962 (Box 15)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 15)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 15)
    - C-648 Natural Products Seminar, 1958-1959 (Box 15)
    - C-648 Seminar in Heterocyclic Chemistry, 1964 (Box 15)
    - C-751 (Box 15)
      - 1946 (Box 15)
      - 1947 (Box 15)
      - 1947 (Box 16)
    - C-752 Course Materials (Box 16)
      - 1947 (Box 16)
      - Undated (Box 16)
    - C-752 General Material, 1946-1947 (Box 16)
    - C-752 Notes (Box 16)
      - 1947-1948 (Box 16)
      - 1949 (Box 16)
    - C-765 Notes, 1947 (Box 16)
    - C-799, 1947 (Box 16)
    - Cavalieri Research Notebook, 1944 (Box 16)
    - Chemical Pharmacology I Materials, 1971-1972 (Box 16)
    - Chemistry Course Bibliography, 1953 (Box 16)
    - Chemistry Course Examinations, 1956-1958 (Box 16)
    - Chemistry Course Materials (Box 16)
      - 1939-1944 (Box 16)
      - 1954-1978 (Box 16)
      - 1979 (Box 16)
      - Undated (Box 16)
    - Chemistry Course Notes (Box 16)
      - 1935-1936 (Box 16)
      - 1938-1940 (Box 16)
      - 1935-1936 (Box 17)
    - Chemistry Course Lecture Notes, 1948 (Box 17)
    - Chemistry Course Materials, 1950-1956 (Box 17)
    - Chemistry Reference Citations, undated (Box 17)
    - Chemistry Course Teaching Materials, undated (Box 17)
    - Chemistry of Steroids Involved in Fertility Regulation Materials, 1971 (Box 17)
    - Course Diagrams, undated (Box 17)
    - Course Examinations, 1941-1953 (Box 17)
    - Course Lectures, 1941-1944 (Box 17)
    - Course Materials (Box 17)
      - 1942-1943 (Box 17)
      - 1950-1951 (Box 17)
      - 1953-1954 (Box 17)
    - Course Notes (Box 17)
      - 1936 (Box 17)
      - 1946-1947 (Box 17)
    - Endocrinology Seminars (Box 17)
      - 1957 (Box 17)
      - 1958-1959 (Box 17)
    - Graduate Preparation Assignment, 1941-1942 (Box 17)
    - Interconversions of Delphinium Alkanoids Lecture, 1957 (Box 17)
    - Lecture Notes, 1942 (Box 17)
    - Lectures Notes (Natural Products), 1958 (Box 18)
    - Natural Products Course Materials, undated (Box 18)
    - Organic Preparation Reports, 1941-1942 (Box 18)
    - Passaic Valley Lecture, 1951 (Box 18)
    - Swarthmore College Honors Examinations, 1943-1947 (Box 18)
- RESTRICTED RECORDS (Box 18)
  - Student Work, 1942-1965
    Note: At this time the sub-series is closed but may be made available with advance notice so that the Archivist may review the specific files requested.
    - D.A. Research Reports, 1951-1952 (Box 18)
    - R.P.B. Thesis Research Notebook, 1951 (Box 18)
    - J.B. Research Notebook and Spectra, 1962 (Box 18)
    - M.B. Research Notebook (Box 18)
      - 1963 (Box 18)
      - 1965 (Box 18)
    - G.B. Research Notebook (Box 18)
      - 1955 (Box 18)
      - 1956-1957 (Box 18)
      - 1957 (Box 18)
    - C.R.B. Research Notebook, 1964 (Box 18)
    - C-109 Graded Test, 1951-1953 (Box 18)
    - R.T.C. Research Notebook, 1962 (Box 18)
    - R.T.C. Data Sheets, 1963 (Box 18)
    - R.T.C. Spectra Graphs, 1962 (Box 18)
    - G.R.C. Research Notebook (Box 18)
      - 1958-1959 (Box 18)
      - 1961 (Box 19)
    - G.F. Research Reports, undated (Box 19)
    - J.H. Research Notebook, 1951-1952 (Box 19)
    - IU Student Recommendations, 1953 (Box 19)
    - W.L. Research Notebook, 1951 (Box 19)
    - E.W.M. Research Notebook, 1947 (Box 19)
    - G.D.M. Research Notebook, 1962 (Box 19)
    - P.M. Research Notebook, 1947 (Box 19)
    - D.J.N. Research Notebook, 1966 (Box 19)
    - J.A.P. Research Notebook, 1948 (Box 19)
    - D.P.B. Research Notebook, 1943 (Box 19)
    - A.R. Research Notebook, 1964 (Box 19)
    - K.S. Research Notebook, 1964 (Box 19)
    - Student Reports, 1942-1943 (Box 19)
    - T.W.S. Infrared Spectra, 1963 (Box 19)
    - T.W.S. Research Notebook (Box 19)
      - 1962 (Box 19)
      - 1965 (Box 19)
    - R.K.T. Research Notebook, 1965 (Box 19)